<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jci Nagpur Metro on </title>
    <link>https://rakeshtembhurne.github.io/hugo-casper-two-rakesh-bhartiya/tags/jci-nagpur-metro/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Jci Nagpur Metro on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://rakeshtembhurne.github.io/hugo-casper-two-rakesh-bhartiya/tags/jci-nagpur-metro/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>JCI Nagpur Metro Organizes a Health Camp</title>
      <link>https://rakeshtembhurne.github.io/hugo-casper-two-rakesh-bhartiya/post/jci-nagpur-metro-organizes-a-health-camp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rakeshtembhurne.github.io/hugo-casper-two-rakesh-bhartiya/post/jci-nagpur-metro-organizes-a-health-camp/</guid>
      <description>My JCI Nagpur Metro Team organized a free Health Checkup, free blood sugar checkup and Blood Pressure checkup Camp on April 7th, 2019 at Jai Durga Bahu Uddeshiya Shikshan Sanstha, Nagpur.
Follwed by the Health Checkup Camp, we took trainings of women at the same venue where more than 150 women were guided on many topics.
JCI Nagpur Metro founder president JFM. G. V. Anand Sharma sir, JCINM Advisor HGF Usha Dhok madam, IPP Rajveer Singh, Sr Member Vijay Kumar sir, active member Tushar Gulhane ji honour us with their presence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I Started This Blog?</title>
      <link>https://rakeshtembhurne.github.io/hugo-casper-two-rakesh-bhartiya/post/why-i-started-this-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rakeshtembhurne.github.io/hugo-casper-two-rakesh-bhartiya/post/why-i-started-this-blog/</guid>
      <description>For so long, I have been working as a techie and I got good expertise over technical things. But somewhere in my mind, I was aware I am being nearer to machines than people. I was feeling that I am no more a social person and hence I had to do something for it.
I started working on social works and getting involved in various organizations. After meeting a lot of people I finally decided that I will work with a few selected organizations.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>